Guide to the Cross & Brown Company Architectural Photograph Collection [1970]-1991 PR 111
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
Cross & Brown Company Architectural Photograph Collection
[1970]-1991
PR 111
@ 2011 New-York Historical Society
4.2 Linear feet (11 boxes)
The Cross & Brown Company architectural photograph collection consists of photographs, negatives, slides, pamphlets, correspondence, and other documents describing or depicting buildings in New York City, New York State, and New Jersey, created by the Cross & Brown Company real estate firm.
Cross & Brown Company
Provenance
Gift of Cross & Brown Company, 1991.
Access Restrictions
Open to qualified researchers.
Photocopying undertaken by staff only. Limited to thirty exposures of stable, unbound material per day. See guidelines in Print Room for details.
Historical Note
Cross & Brown Company was a large New York real estate company that had a "total service" approach to the business. Beginning in 1910 as a real estate brokerage, the company expanded throughout the twentieth century into real estate management, appraisals, consultations, industrial surveys, and other special services. Cross & Brown's headquarters was located in Manhattan from its formation until its acquisition by Insignia Douglas Elliman in 1991. The company's final address was 522 Fifth Avenue. Branch offices were located at 63 Wall Street, and in Long Island City, White Plains (New York), Springfield (New Jersey), and Westport (Connecticut). Cross & Brown was also affiliated with real estate companies across the United States and in Canada. In Manhattan, the company predominantly leased commercial and office buildings, while outside the city the firm concentrated on industrial projects and large commercial ventures.
Scope and Content Note
The Cross & Brown Company Architectural Photograph Collection spans the period from circa 1970 through 1991 and contains photographs, negatives, slides, and documents relating to the company's real estate business. The collection is divided into four series: Photographs; Negatives; Slides; and Documents.
Materials relate primarily to properties in New York City and State, and primarily depict or otherwise describe large buildings. Attractive architectural views of such recognizable structures as the MetLife Tower, the RCA Building, the Pan Am Building (now the MetLife Building), the World Trade Center, and the Plaza Hotel are included. Materials used by Cross & Brown for the development of brochures and other marketing and promotional tools can be found throughout the collection, from photographs and negatives used for illustrations, to slides and notes for presentations. Materials have been arranged into series based on housing and preservation needs, so researchers should check each series for materials relating to a given property.
Arrangement
Materials have been arranged into the following four series based on format:
Series I: Photographs
Series II: Negatives
Series III: Slides
Series IV: Documents
Related Material at the Department of Prints, Photographs, and Architectural Collections
A greater portion of Cross & Brown Company records, including such items as brochures, floor plans, renderings, photographs, and data sheets for specific buildings, are available in the New-York Historical Society Library.
Cross & Brown Company.; Commercial buildings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Contact prints.; Ephemera.; Industrial buildings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Negatives.; New Jersey -- Pictorial works.; New York (N.Y.) -- Pictorial works.; New York (State) -- Pictorial works.; Office buildings -- New York (State) -- New York.; Photographic prints.; Real estate business -- New York (State) -- New York.
- Series I: Photographs
  Scope and Contents note
  Series I is the largest of the series and contains a variety of color and black and white photographs and contact prints. The series is divided into four subseries: Manhattan Properties, New Jersey Properties, New York State Properties, and Cross & Brown Company photographs. Most of these images were used primarily in promotional publications, some of which can be found in Series IV. Most photographs are of building exteriors, but a few interior views are included.
  Photographs of Manhattan buildings date from the early 1970s through 1991, and primarily depict large office buildings. Images are arranged alphabetically by named streets, which are followed by numbered avenues and numbered streets; thereunder photographs are arranged by address.
  The New Jersey Properties subseries consists of only one property, located in northern Bergen County on Livingston Avenue.
  New York State Properties include a variety of sites, mostly commercial or industrial, arranged alphabetically by town. Most are located within a one hundred mile radius of New York City. Properties in the outer boroughs of New York City are included in this subseries, reflecting Cross & Brown's original filing scheme. The largest groupings depict properties in Brooklyn, Queens, and White Plains.
  Company photographs date entirely from the 1980s, and include portraits of Cross & Brown Company employees, arranged alphabetically by name, and photographs of company seminars and meetings, arranged chronologically.
  - Manhattan Properties
    - 163 Allen Street (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - 55 Broad Street (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - 60 Broad Street (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - 120 Broad Street (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - 50 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - 140 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - 165 Broadway (1 Liberty Plaza) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - 222 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - 225 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 250 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 253 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 555 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - 730 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - 1250 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - 1407 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - 1430 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - 1500 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - 1515 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - 1535 Broadway (Marriott Marquis) (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - 1576 Broadway (Castro Building) (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - 1633 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - 1674 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - 1700 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - 1855 Broadway (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - 118 Chambers Street (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 100 Church Street (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 110 Church Street (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 10 Columbus Circle (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 15 Columbus Circle (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 22 Cortlandt Street (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - 1 Dag Hammarskjold Plaza (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - 2 Dag Hammarskjold Plaza (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - 7 Gracie Square (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - 10 Hanover Square (1 Chase Manhattan Plaza) (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - 345 Hudson Street (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - 24 John Street (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - 59 John Street (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - 80 John Street (Box 1, Folder 38)
    - 270 Lafayette Street (Box 1, Folder 39)
    - 360 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 40)
    - 405 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 41)
    - 415 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 42)
    - 485 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - 560 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - 993 Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Miscellaneous Lexington Avenue (Box 1, Folder 46)
    - 1 Liberty Plaza (1 Battery Park Place) (Box 1, Folder 47)
    - 2 Lincoln Square (1 Lincoln Plaza) (Box 1, Folder 48)
    - 1 Madison Avenue (MetLife Tower) (Box 1, Folder 49)
    - 72 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 50)
    - 270 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 51)
    - 275 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 52)
    - 285 Madison Avenue (Young and Rubicam Building) (Box 1, Folder 53)
    - 292 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 54)
    - 295 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 55)
    - 330 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 56)
    - 342 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 57)
    - 345 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 58)
    - 360 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 59)
    - 380 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 60)
    - 415 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 61)
    - 437 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 62)
    - 520 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 63)
    - 535 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 64)
    - 540 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 65)
    - 555 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 66)
    - 575 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 67)
    - 595 Madison Avenue (Fuller Building) (Box 1, Folder 68)
    - 660 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 69)
    - 793 Madison Avenue (Box 1, Folder 70)
    - 59 Maiden Lane (Box 1, Folder 71)
    - 75 Maiden Lane (Box 1, Folder 72)
    - 180 Maiden Lane (Box 1, Folder 73)
    - 208 Mercer Street (Box 1, Folder 74)
    - 2 New York Plaza (Box 1, Folder 75)
    - 4 New York Plaza (Box 1, Folder 76)
    - Park Avenue Plaza (E. 52nd to E. 53rd Streets, between Madison and Park Avenues) (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - 3 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - 90 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - 99 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - 100 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - 200 Park Avenue (Pan Am Building) (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - 230 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - 237 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 84)
    - 270 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - 277 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - 280 Park Avenue (Bankers Trust Plaza) (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - 300 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - 320 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - 345 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - 390 Park Avenue (Lever House) (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - 400 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - 405 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - 410 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - 425-430 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 95)
    - 460 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 96)
    - 475 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 97)
    - 499 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 98)
    - 505 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 99)
    - 1443 Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 100)
    - Miscellaneous Park Avenue (Box 2, Folder 101)
    - 1 and 2 Penn Plaza (Box 2, Folder 102)
    - 80 Pine Street (Box 2, Folder 103)
    - 88 Pine Street (Box 2, Folder 104)
    - 19 Rector Street (Box 2, Folder 105)
    - Rockefeller Center (RCA Building) (Box 2, Folder 106)
    - 1 State Street Plaza (American Express Plaza) (Box 2, Folder 107)
    - 14 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 108)
    - 40 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 109)
    - 45 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 110)
    - 55 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 111)
    - 60 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 112)
    - 63 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 113)
    - 100 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 114)
    - 111 Wall Street (Box 2, Folder 115)
    - 1 Water Street (Box 2, Folder 116)
    - 55 Water Street (Box 2, Folder 117)
    - 77 Water Street (Box 2, Folder 118)
    - 160 Water Street (Box 2, Folder 119)
    - 90 William Street (Box 2, Folder 120)
    - 100 William Street (Box 2, Folder 121)
    - 110 William Street (Box 2, Folder 122)
    - 150 William Street (Box 2, Folder 123)
    - 161 William Street (Box 2, Folder 124)
    - World Trade Center (Box 2, Folder 125)
    - 815 Second Avenue (Box 2, Folder 126)
    - 866 Second Avenue (Box 2, Folder 127)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 2, Folder 128)
    - 600 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 129)
    - 605 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 130)
    - 630 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 131)
    - 685 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 132)
    - 711 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 133)
    - 747 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 134)
    - 750 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 135)
    - 767 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 136)
    - 780 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 137)
    - 805 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 138)
    - 825 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 139)
    - 850 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 140)
    - 866 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 141)
    - 875 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 142)
    - 885 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 143)
    - 900 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 144)
    - 909 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 145)
    - 919 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 146)
    - 964 Third Avenue (Box 2, Folder 147)
    - 122 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 148)
    - 241 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 149)
    - 347 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 150)
    - 521 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 151)
    - 522 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 152)
    - 529 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 153)
    - 530 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 154)
    - 548 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 155)
    - 551 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 156)
    - 555 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 157)
    - 571 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 158)
    - 575 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 159)
    - 592 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 160)
    - 600 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 161)
    - 640 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 162)
    - 665 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 163)
    - 666 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 164)
    - 717 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 165)
    - 725 Fifth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 166)
    - 767 Fifth Avenue (General Motors Building) (Box 3, Folder 167)
    - 768 Fifth Avenue (Plaza Hotel) (Box 3, Folder 168)
    - 1045 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 169)
    - 1114 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 170)
    - 1133 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 171)
    - 1166 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 172)
    - 1180 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 173)
    - 1185 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 174)
    - 1211 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 175)
    - 1230 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 176)
    - 1285 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 177)
    - 1290 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 178)
    - 1345 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 179)
    - 1350 Sixth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 180)
    - 398 Seventh Avenue (Box 3, Folder 181)
    - 729 Seventh Avenue (Box 3, Folder 182)
    - 810 Seventh Avenue (Box 3, Folder 183)
    - 888 Seventh Avenue (Box 3, Folder 184)
    - 441 Ninth Avenue (Box 3, Folder 185)
    - 150 East 3rd Street (Box 3, Folder 186)
    - 227 West 22nd Street (Box 3, Folder 187)
    - 43 West 23rd Street (Box 3, Folder 188)
    - 15-19 East 26th Street (Box 3, Folder 189)
    - East 32nd Street (Box 3, Folder 190)
    - 450 East 33rd Street (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - 7 West 34th Street (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - 22 East 38th Street (Lancaster Hotel) (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - 8 East 40th Street (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - 10 East 40th Street (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - 21 East 40th Street (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - 12 East 41st Street (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - 5 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - 15 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 199)
    - 100 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 200)
    - 201 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 201)
    - 235 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 202)
    - 300 East 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 203)
    - 323 West 42nd Street (Box 3, Folder 204)
    - 11 East 44th Street (Box 3, Folder 205)
    - 144 East 44th Street (Box 3, Folder 206)
    - 8-10 East 45th Street (Box 3, Folder 207)
    - 140 East 45th Street (Box 3, Folder 208)
    - 5 West 45th Street (Charette) (Box 3, Folder 209)
    - 6 East 46th Street (Box 3, Folder 210)
    - 20 East 46th Street (Box 3, Folder 211)
    - 3 West 46th Street (Box 3, Folder 212)
    - 43 West 46th Street (Box 3, Folder 213)
    - 12 East 48th Street (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - 16 East 48th Street (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - 11-17 East 49th Street (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - East 50th Street (at Lexington Avenue) (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - 135 West 50th Street (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - 34 East 51st Street (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - 15 West 51st (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - 40 East 52nd Street (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - 150 East 52nd Street (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - 10 East 53rd Street (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - 39 West 55th Street (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - 126 East 56th Street (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - 155 East 56th Street (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - 165 East 56th Street (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - 3 West 57th Street (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - 111 West 57th Street (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - 555 West 57th Street (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - 4 West 58th Street (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - 304 West 58th Street (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - West 59th Street (St. Moritz Hotel) (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - 45 East 62nd Street (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - 200 East 62nd Street (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - 500 East 62nd Street (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - 36 East 63rd Street (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - 150 72nd Street (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - 4 East 80th Street (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - 2 East 86th Street (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - 12 East 86th Street (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - 201 East 86th Street (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - 253-255 West 93rd Street (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Skyviews (Box 4, Folder 244)
  - New Jersey Properties
    - Bergen County - Livingston Avenue (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - New York State Properties
    - Brewster - 30-50 Main Street, Putnam Terrace Apartments (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Brewster - Brewster Business Park (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - The Bronx - City Island (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - The Bronx - TSS Plaza, corner of Brewster Blvd. and White Planes Road (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Brooklyn - 1025 Atlantic Ave., Spiral Screw Building (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Brooklyn - 80 Dekalb Ave. (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Brooklyn - 380 Henry St. (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - 184 Kent Ave. (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Brooklyn - 1248 Ralph Ave. (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Brooklyn - 470 Vanderbilt Ave. (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Pan-Metal Products, Inc. (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Carle Place - 275 Glen Cove Rd. (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Carmel - Kent Shopping Center (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Elmsford - 33 West Tarrytown Rd., Crossroads Office Building (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Garden City - Avis World Headquarters (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Harrison - 83 Calvert St. (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Haverstraw - Florham Park (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Huntington - Miscellaneous buildings (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Irvington - 100 South Broadway (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Medford - Skyview (Box 4, Folder 265)
    - Newburgh - Skyviews (Box 4, Folder 266)
    - Orangeburg - Glenshaw Glass Plant (Box 4, Folder 267)
    - Patterson - Robin Hill Corporate Park (Box 4, Folder 268)
    - Port Chester - One Gateway Plaza, Village Savings Bank (Box 4, Folder 269)
    - Queens - 115-58 Don Kirk St., Long Island City, Home Care Prod., Inc. (Box 4, Folder 270)
    - Queens - 2100 Hunters Point, Hunters Point Plaza (Box 4, Folder 271)
    - Queens - 288 Morgan Ave., Famous Envelope Co. (Box 4, Folder 272)
    - Queens - Newton Creek, Daily News Building (Box 4, Folder 273)
    - Queens - 32-02 Northern Blvd., Long Island City (Box 4, Folder 274)
    - Queens - 82-33 Queens Blvd., Elmhurst (Box 4, Folder 275)
    - Queens - 92-25 Queens Blvd. (Box 4, Folder 276)
    - Queens - 92-25 Queens Blvd. (Box 4, Folder 277)
    - Queens - 54-35 46th St., Maspeth (Box 4, Folder 278)
    - Queens - 190-03 75th St., Astoria (Box 4, Folder 279)
    - Queens - JFK Airport, Jamaica, Overseas National Airways Building (Box 4, Folder 280)
    - Queens - Long Island City (Box 4, Folder 281)
    - Somers - Route 100, Kipp property (Box 4, Folder 282)
    - Southhampton (Box 4, Folder 283)
    - Suffern - 75 Montebello Rd., Montebello Park, Thomas Fortune Ryan estate (Box 4, Folder 284)
    - Tappan - Tappan Grammar School (Box 4, Folder 285)
    - Watertown - 215 Washington Street (Box 4, Folder 286)
    - Westhampton Beach - Skyviews (Box 4, Folder 287)
    - White Plains - 150 Grand St. (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - White Plains - 360 Mamaroneck Ave. (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - White Plains - 811 North Broadway, Medical Arts Building (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - White Plains - 178 South Fulton Ave. (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - White Plains - 179 Westmoreland Ave. (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - White Plains - White Swan River (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - White Plains - Skyviews (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - White Plains - Miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Yonkers - 480 North Broadway (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Unidentified - Putnam County (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Unidentified - Blue Hill Road (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Unidentified (Box 5, Folder 299)
  - Cross & Brown Company
    - Employees (Box 5, Folder 300-303)
    - Seminars and meetings (Box 5, Folder 304-312)
- Series II: Negatives
  Series II is divided into three subseries: Manhattan Properties, New York State Properties, and Cross & Brown Company photographs. The first two series span the years from the early 1970s until the beginning of the 1990s, while company photographs date exclusively from the 1980s. Manhattan properties are arranged alphabetically by street, followed numerically by numbered avenues and then numbered streets. New York State Properties are arranged alphabetically by town (or borough). As in Series I, buildings in New York City's outer boroughs are filed under New York State. Cross & Brown Company photographs are filed by name of individual or event, as in Series I.
  - Manhattan Properties
    - 163 Allen Street (Box 6, Folder 313)
    - 82 Beaver Street (Cocoa Exchange) (Box 6, Folder 314)
    - 55 Broad Street (Box 6, Folder 315)
    - 60 Broad Street (Box 6, Folder 316)
    - 120 Broad Street (Box 6, Folder 317)
    - 50 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 318)
    - 71 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 319)
    - 140 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 320)
    - 222 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 321)
    - 225 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 322)
    - 250 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 323)
    - 555 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 324)
    - 730 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 325)
    - 1141 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 326)
    - 1407 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 327)
    - 1430 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 328)
    - 1500 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 329)
    - 1515 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 330)
    - 1576 Broadway (Castro Building) (Box 6, Folder 331)
    - 1674 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 332)
    - 1855 Broadway (Box 6, Folder 333)
    - 100 Church Street (Box 6, Folder 334)
    - 110 Church Street (Box 6, Folder 335)
    - 10 Columbus Circle (Box 6, Folder 336)
    - 15 Columbus Circle (Box 6, Folder 337)
    - 22 Cortlandt Street (Box 6, Folder 338)
    - 1 Dag Hammarskjold Plaza (Box 6, Folder 339)
    - 2 Dag Hammarskjold Plaza (Box 6, Folder 340)
    - 7 Gracie Square (Box 6, Folder 341)
    - 10 Hanover Square (1 Chase Manhattan Plaza) (Box 6, Folder 342)
    - 24 John Street (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - 59 John Street (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - 270 Lafayette Street (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - 360 Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 346)
    - 415 Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 347)
    - 485 Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 348)
    - 560 Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 349)
    - 993 Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 350)
    - Miscellaneous - Lexington Avenue (Box 6, Folder 351)
    - 1 Liberty Plaza (1 Battery Park Place) (Box 6, Folder 352)
    - 2 Lincoln Square (1 Lincoln Plaza) (Box 6, Folder 353)
    - 1 Madison Avenue (MetLife Tower) (Box 6, Folder 354)
    - 72 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 355)
    - 220 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 356)
    - 270 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 357)
    - 275 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 358)
    - 285 Madison Avenue (Young and Rubicam Building) (Box 6, Folder 359)
    - 295 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 360)
    - 330 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 361)
    - 342 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 362)
    - 345 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 363)
    - 360 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 364)
    - 380 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 365)
    - 415 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 366)
    - 437 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 367)
    - 520 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - 535 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - 540 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - 575 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - 595 Madison Avenue (Fuller Building) (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - 650 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - 660 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - 793 Madison Avenue (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - 59 Maiden Lane (Box 7, Folder 376)
    - 75 Maiden Lane (Box 7, Folder 377)
    - 180 Maiden Lane (Box 7, Folder 378)
    - 2 New York Plaza (Box 7, Folder 379)
    - 4 New York Plaza (Box 7, Folder 380)
    - Plaza - Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 381)
    - 90 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 382)
    - 99 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 383)
    - 100 Park Avenue (Box 7, Folder 384)
    - 200 Park Avenue (Pan Am Building) (Box 7, Folder 385)